pluginprofitsite.com 2019-07-07

# PRIVACY POLICY

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY**

This privacy policy tells you how Plug-In Profit Site (“we”) collect, use, and protect your personal information. By visiting our website you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. In particular, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.

**MINORS**

We do not provide services or sell products to children. If you are below the age of 18, you may use our website only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor, please do not provide us or other website visitors with any personal information.

**POLICY IS PART OF OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE**

Our privacy policy is part of, and subject to, our website's terms and conditions of use. You may view these terms and conditions on our website.

**THE TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU**

Like most places on the Internet, simply by visiting our website you automatically tell us certain information. This includes basic information such as your IP address, when you visited, the website from where you came prior to visiting us, the website where you go when you leave our website, your computer's operating system, and the type of web browser that you are using. Our website automatically records this basic information about you.

And like many other websites, we may use cookies. In plain English, this means information that our website's server transfers to your computer. This information can be used to track your session on our website. Cookies may also be used to customize our website content for you as an individual. If you are using one of the common Internet web browsers, you can set up your browser to either let you know when you receive a cookie or to deny cookie access to your computer.

We may also collect any data that you provide us by e-mail. This may include, but not limited to, your name and email address. You can always choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to some or all of our website's services and features.

The use of cookies by our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is/is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do/do not have access or control over these cookies.  Our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] use session ID cookies [to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.]  

**WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION**

We use your information to operate our website's business activities. For example, we may use this data to contact you about changes to our website, new services, or special offers, resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues, and enforce our website's terms and conditions.

As a general rule, we will not give your data to third parties without your permission. However, there are some important exceptions to this rule that are described in the following paragraphs.

We may, in our sole discretion, provide information about you to law enforcement or other government officials for purposes of fraud investigations, alleged intellectual property infringement, or any other suspected illegal activity or matters that may expose us to legal liability. If Plug-In Profit Site is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.  

Although we do not disclose individually identifiable information, we may disclose aggregate data about our website's visitors to advertisers or other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes.

From time to time, we may use third party suppliers to provide services on our website. If a supplier wants to collect information about you, you will be notified. However, you will never be required to give information to a third party supplier. We restrict the way third party suppliers can use your information. They are not allowed to sell or give your information to others.

**USER NAMES AND PASSWORDS**

Your access to parts of our website may be protected by a user name and a password. Do not give your password to anyone. If you enter a section of our website that requires a password, you should log out when you leave. As a safety precaution, you should also close out of your web browser completely and re-open it before viewing other parts of the Internet.

**SECURITY  
**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
**  
****USER ACCESS AND CHOICE**

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, ask to have it removed by making the change on our member information page or by [contacting our help desk](http://support.pluginprofitsite.com/), or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.  We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**YOUR USE OF INFORMATION AND UNSOLICITED JUNK E-MAIL**

If you obtain personal information about another website user, you are not allowed to disclose this information to anyone else without the consent of the user and our consent too.

We hate junk e-mail (Spam). Information you obtain from our website about us or other site users cannot be used by you or others to send unsolicited commercial e-mail or to send unsolicited commercial communications via our website's posting or other communication systems. 

**YOUR VOLUNTARY DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES WHO ARE NOT OUR SUPPLIERS**

You may choose to provide personal information to website visitors or other third parties who are not our suppliers. Please use caution when doing so. The privacy policies and customs of these third parties determine what is done with your information.

**LINKS TO 3RD PARTY SITES  
**

Our website includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Plug-In Profit Site If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

 **TESTIMONIALS**

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements.  With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us [here](http://support.pluginprofitsite.com/).

**AUTORESPONDERS**

We may use autoresponders to communicate with you by e-mail. To protect your privacy, we use a verified opt-in system for such communications and you can always opt-out of such communications using the links contained in each autoresponder message. If you have difficulties opting out, you may [contact us here](http://support.pluginprofitsite.com/), or send us mail to the address listed below. 

**POLICY CHANGES**

The terms of this policy may change from time to time. If such changes are made, we will notify you by a notice posted on our website's home page of the changes that have been made prior to the change becoming effective. If you disagree with the changes that have been made, please contact us (by e-mail, using a website contact form, or in writing by mail), and any changes made to this policy will not apply to information we have collected from you prior to making the changes.

If you are concerned about the topic covered by this policy, you should read it each time before you use our website. Any questions or concerns about this policy should be brought to our attention by [contacting our help desk](http://support.pluginprofitsite.com/) and providing us with information relating to your concern.

You may also mail your concerns to us at the following address:

Stone Evans  
18208 Preston Rd.  
Ste D-9 #311  
Dallas, TX 75252  
USA

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

If you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83 permits you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, [contact us here](http://support.pluginprofitsite.com/) or write us at the mailing address listed above.

Copyright © Stone Evans, The Home Biz Guy  
All rights reserved worldwide.
